Emmanuel Gonzalez

emmanuel.gonzalez.careers@gmail.com (925) 663 5601 Concord, CA

WORK EXPERIENCE

Propark Mobility

Valet Supervisor, April 2021 - Present

- Deliver excellent customer service in a fast paced environment
- Cooperate with upper management and associates to execute day to day tasks
- Carry out instructions from upper management
- Retrieve guests vehicles in an efficient time

Geek Squad

Repair Agent, Dec 2023 - May 2024

- Troubleshoot/Install PC Hardware and Software such as motherboards, cpu, ram and hard drives
- Migrate user data from one pc to another
- Setup Data Backups using windows and macOS
- Use ticketing system to navigate queue of work orders

Towne Park

Valet Associate Aug 2017 - March 2020

- Assist guests with their luggage
- Park and retrieve vehicles

SKILLS

- Basic understanding of networking protocols such as: TCP, UDP, DHCP
- Packet analysis via Kali Linux WireShark
- Windows / Linux Operating System Installation and navigation
- Familiar with modern software such as Microsoft 365
- Bilingual in Spanish
- Clear cut communication
- Patient and Adaptability

EDUCATION

CompTIA A+ in progress for June 2024

Diablo Valley College - Pleasant Hill, CA Associate of Science Computer Science

ABOUT

I have close to a decade of customer service experience by working in front end environments such as valet, cashier & server. I'm great at talking to people, easy going and getting along with everyone. Good with numbers, software and learning new technologies. Looking to pursue a role in a more technical/ skill oriented field.